RESUME OF HAMIDUL ISLAM

Contact address: 383/2/D Free School Street,

Hatirpool, Dhanmondi, Dhaka -1205. Contact Phone Number: +8801682-946614,

Email: h.i.nouhal@gmail.com



• Career Objective :

To work in an international standard and renowned organization in any suitable position for an opportunity to learn, grow, and eventually taken greater responsibility and to face the challenge of the time and gain experience for a successful career.

• Career Summary:

Serving as an Executive-Accounts & Finance for 4.1 years and continuing at Gramsico. Responsibilities here are Stock Management Accounts, Entry level work, Commercial work, Commercial & General Banking, LC, Showrooms operation. Etc.

Have experience as a Data Entry Operator at IIML, Dhaka.

• Special Qualification:

Team Building, Team Leading, Computer literature, Tour Operate, Communication, Graphics Design, Mobile Photography.

• Social Activities :

- Blood Donor & Member of "Roktodaner Opekkhay Bangladesh" Facebook Group.
- Admin & Tour Host of "Ghurghur Ghuranti" a Travel Group.
- Admin & Alumni member, Reunion Organizer of "Uttara Model College" Facebook Group.
- Work with multi organizations for fund collection for poor people & diseases patients.

• Employment History :

Total Year of Experience: 6.5 Year(s)

• Sr. Executive – Accounts & Finance (January 2021 - Continuing)

GRAMSICO

Company Location: 235/1 Elephant road, Dhaka-1205

Department: Accounts & Finance

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Stock Management Accounts.
- Update stock info by inventory.
- Commercial Banking.
- General Banking.
- Prepare or update reports assign by management.
- LC opening & maintaining documents.
- Showroom Operations, Etc.



• Executive – Accounts & Finance (August 8, 2016 – December 2020)

GRAMSICO

Company Location: 235/1 Elephant road, Dhaka-1205

Department: Accounts & Finance

Duties/Responsibilities:

Stock Management Accounts.

- Update stock info by inventory.
- General Banking.
- Commercial Banking.
- Prepare or update reports assign by management
- Update daily activities and report it to the management.

• Project Supervisor (March 2015 – July 2016)

AR OUTSOURCING FIRM

Company Location: Dakkhinkhan, Uttara, Dhaka-1230.

Department: Outsourcing *Duties/Responsibilities:*

- Supervised to all of Outsourcing Employee.
- Team Organize & Building.
- Communication with Client.
- Project Furnish.
- Human Resource.
- Prepare & Update Weekly & Monthly Report, Etc.

• Data Entry Operator (February 2014 – February 2015)

INTELLIGENT IMAGE MANAGEMENT LIMITED, an ISO Certified Company.

Company Location: Baridhara DOHS, Dhaka.

Department: Production *Duties/Responsibilities:*

- Data Entry
- Information Collection
- Data Collection & Processing,

• Computer Skills :

MS Office Package (Specially MS Word, Excel & PowerPoint), Accounting Software Tally, Data Entry, Networking, Internet Browsing, Emailing, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Etc.

• Banking Skills:

Experience of Official Banking, Cash Deposit, Cash Withdraw, Account Payee Transaction, LC, Commercial Banking.

• Training Summary:

Training Title	Topic	Institute	Country	Location	Year	Duration
Software	Data	Intelligent Image	Dhaka,	Baridhara DOHS,	2014	03 Months
	Entry	Management Limited	Bangladesh	Dhaka.		

• ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Exam Title	Concentration /Major	Institute	Result	Pass Year	Duration	Achievement
Masters of Business Administration (MBA)	Management	University of Dhaka	Appeared		1 year	
Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)	Management	University of Dhaka	CGPA:2.82 out of 4	2016	4 years	
HSC	Business Studies	Uttara Model College	GPA:4.6 out of 5	2012	2 years	Best Students Award
SSC (Dakhil)	Humanities	Dadhiar Char Charmadhua Nama Para Dakhil Madrasah	GPA:5 out of 5	2010		Nakla Foundation Award

• Language Proficiency:

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Bangla	Excellent	Excellent	Excellent
English	Good	Excellent	Good

• PERSONAL INFORMATIONS:

Father's Name : Hasur Uddin
Mother's Name : Rokeya Begum

Permanent Address: Vill- Gourdwar, P/O- Gourdwar, P/S- Nakla, Dist- Sherpur.

Present Address: 383/2/D Free School Street, Hatirpool, Dhaka-1205.

Contact Phone No : +880 1682-946614 **Date of Birth** : 5th June, 1994

Sex : Male

Place of Birth : Nakla, Sherpur, Bangladesh.

Religion : Islam

Nationality : Bangladeshi (by Birth)

Marital Status : Unmarried

Hobbies: Traveling, Reading, Writing, Debating, etc.

• References:

1. Md. Hedayet Ali

Sr. Manager (Accounts & Finance)

GRAMSICO

235/1, Elephant Road, Dhaka.

Cell: 01673 474809

2. Md. Nuru Miah

Manager (Finance, Accounts & Vat) Paragon Ceramic Industries Limited H# 32, Rd# 1/A, Block-J, Baridhara.

Cell: 01755 621028

• Signature:

Salay

Hamidul Islam

Date: